Guide to Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University, student records
1960-2012
RU 133
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
125.17
(181 Boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University.
Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-H-1 (YRG 13-H-1), Records of the dean of Jonathan Edwards College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Jonathan Edwards College, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Impounded student records for the Classes of 1975-1978, Accession 1975-A-017
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2050
  - Class of 1975
    - JE - Classes of 1975, 1976, 1977 Student File Letters (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1975 Counselor Reports (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1976
    - Class of 1976 Counselor Reports, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Class of 1977
    - Class of 1977 - Counselor Reports, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Class of 1978
- Student records for students withdrawn from the Classes of 1975-1978, Accession 1980-A-023
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - 1975
  - 1976
  - 1977 -1978
- Student records for the Classes of 1975-1976, 1971-1976; Accession 1980-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  - 1975
  - 1976
- Student records for the Classes of 1951-1974, Accession 1980-A-036
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
  - Class of 1951
  - Class of 1956
  - Class of 1957
  - Class of 1958
  - Class of 1959
  - Class of 1960
    - Ex Students (Class of 1960), 1956-1960
  - Class of 1961
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1962
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1963
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1964
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1965
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1967
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1968
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1969
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1970
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1971
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1972
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1973
    - Ex-Students
  - Class of 1974
    - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1977, 1973-1977; Accession 1981-A-043
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
- Student records for the Class of 1978, 1974-1978; Accession 1982-A-041
- Student records for the Class of 1979, 1975-1979; Accession 1983-A-071
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1980, 1976-1980; Accession 1984-A-044
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1981, 1977-1981; Accession 1985-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1982, 1978-1982; Accession 1987-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1983, 1979-1983; Accession 1987-A-113
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1984, 1980-1984; Accession 1990-A-007
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1985, 1981-1985; Accession 1990-A-028
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1986, 1982-1986; Accession 1991-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Ex- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1987, 1983-1987; Accession 1992-A-008
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1988, 1984-1988; Accession 1993-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1989, 1985-1989; Accession 1994-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1990, 1986-1990; Accession 1994-A-121
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1991, 1987-1991; Accession 1995-A-077
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1992, 1988-1992; Accession 1997-A-007
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1993, 1989-1993; Accession 1998-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1994, 1990-1994; Accession 1999-A-002
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Ex-student
- Student records for the Class of 1995, 1991-1995; Accession 1999-A-097
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1996, 1992-1996; Accession 2001-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1997, 1993-1997; Accession 2001-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1998, 1994-1998; Accession 2003-A-134
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1999, 1995-1999; Accession 2003-A-135
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 2000, 1996-2000; Accession 2004-A-142
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - (Incomplete), 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Withdrawn, 1996-2000
  - Deceased
- Student records for the Class of 2001, 1997-2001; Accession 2006-A-131
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Class of 2002, 1998-2002; Accession 2006-A-130
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
  - Deceased
  - Non-Grad
  - Withdrew
- Student records for the Classes of 2003-2004, 1999-2004; Accession 2007-A-073
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2080
  Arranged by class, thereunder alphabetically by last name.
  - Class of 2003
  - Class of 2004
  - DID NOT GRADUATE
  - WITHDRAWALS
- Student records for the Class of 2005, 2001-2005; Accession 2011-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2081
- Student Records for the Class of 2006, 1995-2007; Accession 2012-A-016
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2082
- Student records for the Class of 2007, Accession 2015-A-015
  Restricted until January 1, 2082
- Student records for the Class of 2008, 2003-2012; Accession 2016-A-031
  Restricted until January 1, 2083
- Student records for the Class of 2009, Accession 2017-A-017
  Restricted until January 1, 2085
- Student records for the Class of 2010, Accession 2018-A-022
  Restricted until January 1, 2076
- Student records for the Class of 2011, Accession 2019-A-0012
  Restricted until January 1, 2087
  - Aquino, Mariel, 2006-2011 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ashforth, Megan, 2008-2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barrosse-Antle, Mary, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bethel, Timeica, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biagiotti, Jonathan, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Blumenfeld, Steven, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Botwinick, Nathaniel, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bronfin, Michael, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Broockman, David, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brownlee, Sarah, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cannon, Kelly, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Casablanca, Roberto, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chafkin, Isabelle, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chammas, Sheide, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chandler, Thomas, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chen, Cecelia, 2006-2011 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Choe, So Yeon, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Choy, Matthew, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cole, Alan, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Coleman, Patrick, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Colt, Susanna, 2007-2007 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Culakova, Zuzana, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dalal, Rahul, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Darwin, Kristin, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Diamond, Daniel, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Diamond, William, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Eastman, Vera, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Eaton, Elliot, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Elser, Joshua, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Eng, Jonathan, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fackler, Erin, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Farmer, Miranda, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gillon, Alexandra, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Goldfarb, Stephanie, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hecht, Benjamin, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hernandez, Adrea, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hilton, Sean, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hodgkins, Alice, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Howe, Dennis, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Jackson, Nicole, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Jacobson, Hannah, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Jaye, Rebecca, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Derek, 2006-2011 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Keitel, Courtney, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Kelleher, Matthew, 2006-2011 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kidd, Fielding, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Koh, Darell, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Kreidberg, Laura, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kuschner, Rachel, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Lalwani, Naishadh, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Lao, Daniel, 2007-2011 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lash, Christopher, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Laudone, Claire, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lerner-Byars, Tess, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lew, Catherine, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Li, Corinna, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Libresco, Leah, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Lim, Young, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Lucos, Ileana, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lufkin, Sophia, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Luong, Nancy, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mahbubani, Shelagh, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Manchanda, Aashish, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mantilla, Rafael, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Martinez, Devon, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Martinez Bernardino, Hugo, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mastroyannis, Spyridon, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - McFadden, Nikia, 2009-2011 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Meyer, Eric, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Miller, Zeke, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Moncharsh, Anna, 2006-2011 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Money, Adam, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Munyan, Katie, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Newman, Daniel, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Nghiem, Darina, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Paulino, Edward, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pavlenko, Nikita, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Pichardo, Lusdymer, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Qadri, Umar, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Reeves, Elizabeth, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Richey, Jason, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, Allison, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Rosetti, Chloe, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Rozansky, Hallie, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Scavone, Christopher, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Selz, Nicholas, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Shadunsky, Yuri, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Shen, Diana, 2006-2011 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Silva, Maxwell, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Spock, Randall, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Tann, Nigel, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Thangaraj, Phyllis, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Tortorello, Gabriella, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Tran, Thanh Tien, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Trivellas, Andromahi, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Trupin, Rebecca, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Valdes, Lianna, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Vu, Quoc-Kha Kelvin, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Walsh, Daniel, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Watanabe, Kisho, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Wigdor, Jared, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Winsberg, Sarah, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Wong, Victor, 2005-2011 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Wood, Samuel, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Yang, Jingying, 2006-2011 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Yang, Sherry, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Zhu, Charles, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Zhu, Yinong, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 13)